eacdirectory.co.ke 2015-06-23

# EACdirectory | Privacy and Refund Policies

### Collection

We collect your personal information when you register or enter information on our site. We use cookies and other technology to keep track of your online interaction with our site.The information that you provide to us is within a secure environment (through encryption)

### Information use

We use information to do the following:

  1. Provide the requested services.
  2. Personalize the site for you, communicate with you, and offer you special promotions.
  3. Help enforce our terms and conditions, prevent fraud, and keep our Web site safe.

### Disclosure

We disclose your information to facilitate your transactions on the site. We occasionally provide information to other companies who work on our behalf to help provide our services. We share limited information with law enforcement and others to help keep our service safe.

### Notification preferences

You can choose how we communicate with you by entering your details when signing up. We shall use both email and telephone modes for Kenyans and emails for other nationalities. Click [here](https://www.eac.eacdirectory.co.ke/clientarea.php "Client area") You can access, review, and change your personal information from the client area.

### Other information

We don’t send spam and do not permit spam on EACdirectory website and related servers. Learn more about keeping your online identity safe; go to our Security and Resolution Center for more information.

### Changes to this privacy policy

EACdirectory may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the email address specified in your account.

**Note:  **EACdirectory shall never send you emails asking for personal information like password, credit card information. We use a third party company (2Checkout.Com) for processing and collecting payments from your credit card/paypal account. Please [visit this link](http://www.2checkout.com/documentation/privacy.htm) for their privacy terms.

Note that 2Checkout.com is an authorized reseller of goods and services provided by EACdirectory.Click [here](http://www.2checkout.com/language_guidelines.html "2checkout note") for More information **.  
**

### Refund policy

Because of the nature of services we offer, there is no refund that shall be given.

**Alternative Payments** : Refunds will be issued for credit card /Paypal related payments ONLY. This willl be as a substitute for MPESA or Cash. This window is available for 24 hours only. The MPESA or Cash Payment Must be made and received by EACdirectory before an reversal of credit card/ Debit card or paypal.

EACdirectory is a Kenic accredited registrar for.co.ke domains.  
We are the largest kenyan domain registrar ( **.co.ke, and other extensions.** ) We also provide cpanel web hosting in kenya
